// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Mohan is twice as old as his brother. 3 years ago, Mohan's age was 3 times his brothers age. Calculate Mohan's present age.",
    answer: "12",
    options: ["6", "14", "12", "16"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "Five years ago the sum of the ages of A and B was 58 years. The difference between B's age 8 years ago and A's age 8 years hence is 16 years. The ratio of the present ages of A and B is:",
    answer: "9:25",
    options: ["9:25", "25/9", "5:13", "36:52"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "P is as much younger to Q as he is older to R. If the sum of the ages of Q and R is 72 years. What is the age of P",
    answer: "36 Years",
    options: ["16 Years", "36 Years", "26 Years", "46 Years"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "Daughter's present age is 2/5 in the comparison of her mother .8 year later , age of her daughter will be 1/2 in the comparison of her mother. Find out mother present age?",
    answer: "40",
    options: ["38", "40", "42", "44"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "Ten years ago, P was half of Q's age. If the ratio of their present ages is 3 ∶ 4, what will be total of their present ages?",
    answer: "35",
    options: ["45", "30", "35", "44"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "20 year old Manish is five times as old as his brother Greece. How old will Manish be when he is three times as old as Greece?",
    answer: "24",
    options: ["30", "32", "24", "28"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "After 15 years, a man will be just four times as old as he was 15 years ago. What is his present age?",
    answer: "25 Years",
    options: ["10 Years", "15 Years", "20 Years", "25 Years"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "The ratio of ages of Rahul and his wife after 7 years from now will be 7 ∶ 6. If his wife was born 23 years ago, find the age of Rahul after 2 years?",
    answer: "6 Years",
    options: ["4 Years", "6 Years", "8 Years", "2 Years"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "After 5 years, the ratio between ages of A and B will be 5 : 8 and after 8 years, the sum of ages will be 71 years. Find the present age of B.",
    answer: "35 Years",
    options: ["33 Years", "35 Years", "32 Years", "40 Years"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "The average age of a man and his wife at the time of their marriage was 27 years. After 4 years of marriage, they have a one-year-old child. The average age of the family now is?",
    answer: "21 Years",
    options: ["24 Years", "23 Years", "21 Years", "19 Years"],
  },
];
